{
    "id": "85c01ea6a90041e49f4275e1bed3c1f2",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… sure that she is lying.",
            "description": "When feel is used to talk about reactions and opinions, it is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "feel",
                "am feeling"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You are ………………………… a wonderful person!",
            "description": "In exclamations, we use such before an adjective + plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That was ……………………….. kind of you.",
            "description": "So is used before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. to get a raise this year.",
            "description": "Before an indirect object, wait and hope are followed by for.",
            "answers": [
                "expect",
                "hope",
                "wait"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You must not use someone ……………………….. ideas in your essay.",
            "description": "Else has a possessive form – else’s.",
            "answers": [
                "else",
                "else's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ………………………. tired to walk.",
            "description": "Too is not used with much before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The students were completely …………………………… after the expedition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "exhausting",
                "exhausted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I had no difficulty ………………………………. his house.",
            "description": "Difficulty is followed by in + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to find",
                "in finding"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The whole village was ……………………….. water.",
            "description": "We use under when something is covered by what is over it.",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The house requires a lot of repairs ………………………., it is too small.",
            "description": "Besides means in addition to.",
            "answers": [
                "beside",
                "besides"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The car won’t ………………………….. again.",
            "description": "We make machines start.",
            "answers": [
                "begin",
                "start"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If she had been here, she ………………………………… happy to hear this.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if clause and would have + past participle in the main clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "would be",
                "will be",
                "would have been"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}